export let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Lisa and Max are Americans. ______ from U.S.A",
    answer: "They’re",
    options: ["There", "Their", "They’re", "Their’re"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I ______ 22 years old, but Andrew ______ 20.",
    answer: "am / is",
    options: ["am / am", "are / am", "am / is", "are / are"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: ". Oxford is ______ English university",
    answer: "an",
    options: ["an", "*", "the", "a"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "I went to university, _____ Sandy didn’t.",
    answer: "but",
    options: ["until", "so", "but", "and"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "My sister has graduated from the University.",
    answer: "So has his brother",
    options: [
      "So is my sister",
      "Her sister has either",
      "So has his brother",
      "Neither did mine",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Actors have to _______ a play before they give a public performance.",
    answer: "rehearse",
    options: ["practice", "repeat", "rehearse", "prepare"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Rosemary _____ three languages.",
    answer: "speaks",
    options: ["speaks", "talks", "tells", "know"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Their son _____ in this hospital.",
    answer: "works",
    options: ["works", "begins", "starts", "likes"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Ann is _____ wife",
    answer: "John’s",
    options: ["John’s", " John is", " John’s is", "John"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "They’re not his _____ mistakes",
    answer: "friend’s",
    options: ["friend’s", "friend", "friends", "friends’s"],
  },
];
